[Music]
you always try to give the best in life
to your loved ones
beat education for your
child vacations
are a better lifestyle for your family
you ensure that you and your loved ones
get happiness and comfort
but life as we know is full of
uncertainties
rising inflation future health care
costs
and taxes may further reduce your income
that's why you need a plan that can give
you guaranteed returns in the form of
regular income and help you achieve your
life goals presenting icici pro
guaranteed income for tomorrow long term
a plan that provides you tax-free
guaranteed income for 15 20 25 or 30
years as per your needs you can avail a
host of benefits such as life insurance
cover for the entire policy term
including the income period guaranteed
income to secure your goals tax benefits
on premiums paid and benefits received
icici pro guaranteed income for tomorrow
long term comes with two options let's
understand these options in detail
income option pay premiums for 7 or 10
years and choose to receive guaranteed
income for 15 20 25 or 30 years
income with 110 rop option
pay premiums for 7 or 10 years and
choose to receive guaranteed income for
15 20 25 or 30 years
along with the last income you also get
back 110 of the total premiums paid by
you
you can also choose to take income
annually or monthly as per your needs
what's more save the date feature lets
you select any special date of your
choice to start receiving guaranteed
income
no matter how uncertain life be you can
always plan it
so what are you waiting for enjoy every
small and big moment with your loved
ones and fulfill your responsibilities
and aspirations with icici pro
guaranteed income for tomorrow long term
[Music]